A Guide to the Virginia Electric and Power Company Records, 1849-ca. 1995
Library of Virginia
- General Counsel and Vice President Files, 1887-1942, 14.4 cubic feet (Box 1-32)
  - Legal Files, 1903-1942, 11.475 cubic feet (Box 3-27)
    - Cobb, Laura L., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Coca-Cola Bottling Works, case of, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Cockrell, L. E., 1917 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Codd, Paul B., case of, 1915-1916 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Cohen, Celia, case of, 1922 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Cohen Grocery and Liquor Company, case of, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Cohen, Louis, case of, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Cole, J. Edward, case of, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Cole, James W., case of, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Collier, Russell W., case of, 1920-1921 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Collins, William, case of, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Colonial Place Corporation, contract with, 1909-1920 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Committee on Public Relations, resolution establishing, n. d. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Constantopolous, James, case of, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Conwell, W. W., 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Cook, Nettie E., case of, 1917-1918 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Cooke, Thomas, case of, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Coplan, Oscar, case of, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Corbitt Motor Truck Company, case of, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Coward, Mabel Thayer, case of, 1921 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Crall, Elma, case of, 1922 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Crawford and First Street (Portsmouth) Line, proposed abandonment of, 1912-1919 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Crawford, Claire E. and Frances Sykes, case of, 1917-1918 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Crawfords Bay Terminal (Norfolk) property sale proposition, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Crobarger, G. P. and Lee Spencer, case of, 1918, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Cross, William H. (administrator of Georgia Wallace), case of, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Crouch, C. C., case of, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Crowded streetcars, 1913 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Crum, W. W., case of, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Crump, Mary D. (administrator of Mary Virginia Shiflett), case of (B1509), 1919-1923 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Crump, Mary D. (administrator of Mary Virginia Shiflett), case of (B1398), 1919 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Cuffee, C. T. (adminstrator of Earl Coleman), case of, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Cullingsworth, V. S., case of, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Culpepper, A. W., case of, 1920-1921 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Cummings, Ethel, case of, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Curran, Alleine W., case of, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Custis, J. R., case of, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Cutchin, William H., case of, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Cuthrell, Jesse E., case of, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Cases: General - D, 1921-1925 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Darley, C. E., case of, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Davenport, Helen, case of, 1920-1922 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Davidson, C. E., case of, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Davis, Albert F., case of, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), April 1919 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), May-October 1919 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), November-December 1919 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), January-April 1920 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), May-December 1920 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), January-November 1921 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), December 1921 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), January 1922 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), February-April 1922 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), May-July 1922 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), August-September 1922 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), October 1922 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), November-December 1922 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B10), January-April 1923 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (memorandum of authorities)(B10), 1919 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (miscellaneous court documents)(B10), 1919-1921 (Box 9, Folder 2-6)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (witness' testimony)(B10), 1919 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (B11), June 1909 (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B11), August-September 1909 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B11), October-December 1909 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B11), January-March 1910 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B11), April 1910 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B11), June-December 1910 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B11), February 1911-May 1913 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B11), October 1913 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B11), January 1914 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B11), June 1914 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), July 1914 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), August 1914 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), September-November 1914 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), December 1914-January 1915 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), February-March 1915 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), April-June 1915 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), November 1915 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), December 1915-January 1916 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), February-March 1916 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), April 1916 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), May-June 1916 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), July 1916-February 1917 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), March-May 1917 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), June 1917 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), July 1917 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), August-October 1917 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), November-December 1917 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), January 1918 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), February 1918 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), March-April 1918 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), May-June 1918 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), July 1918 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), August-September 1918 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), October-November 1918 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), January-February 1919 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), March-April 1919 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), November-December 1919 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), January 1920 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), February 1920 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), March 1920 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), May 1920 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), June-October 1920 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), November 1920 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), December 1920-January 1921 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), February-May 1921 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, cases of (B12), December 1921-December 1922 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (abstract of argument)(B12), 1915 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (affidavits)(B12), 1916, 1920 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (briefs)(B12), 1915 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (briefs)(B12), 1921 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (memorandum of argument)(B12), n. d. (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (memorandum of authorities)(B12), 1914 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (memorandum of errors and corrections)(B12), 1918-1919 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (oral argument)(B12), 1910 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (petition for rehearing)(B12), n. d. (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - Davis, Charles Hall, case of (right of appeal)(B12), 1922 (Box 12, Folder 9a)
    - Davis, Rosa, case of, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Davis, Shelton W., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Davis, W. C., case of, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Davis, W. L., case of, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Deferred classification for Virginia Railway and Power Company employees to avoid war service, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Derring, P. L. (administrator for A. J. Derring), case of, 1915-1918 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Derring, P. L. (administrator for A. J. Derring), case of (brief), 1916 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Dey, T. M., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Diamantes, A., case of, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Dixie Paper Mills Company, case of, 1918-1919 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Donaldson, Paul, case of, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Doran, Edward J., deed of, 1914 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Dowdy, Laura C. and Chester J. Martin, cases of, 1917-1918 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Dressler, Naomi C., case of, 1918-1921 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Driscoll, Maude M., case of, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Dubinsky, Lee, case of, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Duer, Mary C., case of, 1917-1918 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Dunkan, John, case of, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Durrett, J. H., case of, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Cases: General - E, 1923-1924 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Earle, Mary Jane M., case of, 1920-1922 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - East, Ida W., case of, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Eastern Motor Sales Corporation, case of, 1915-1916 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Eddleton, Ruth, case of, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Edwards, George, case of, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Eggleston, Gus, case of, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - 18th Street (Norfolk) paving, 1913 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Eisenberger, George W., case of, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Elder, Maggie A., case of, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Electrical appliance repair service liability, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Electrolysis (Chicago), case of, 1913 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Ellis, Lillie P., case of, 1919-1921 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Emporia Hydro Electric Power Corporation purchase examination, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Epps, J. C., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Erickson, Clarence, case of, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Etheridge, H. L., case of, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Etheridge, Mattie R., case of, 1918-1919 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Eubank, W. T., case of, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Evans, Edward A., case of, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Cases: General - F, 1922-1925 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Facenda, A. J., case of, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Fairmount Park (Norfolk), case of, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Farmer, Ola, case of, 1922-1925 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Farmville electric light and power plant acquisition and operation, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Federal income and electricity taxes, correspondence with senators concerning, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Federal Reserve Bank conduit damages, case of, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Federal Reserve Bank conduit damages, case of, January-April 1923 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Federal Reserve Bank conduit damages, case of, May-October 1923 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Fehsenfeld, William H., Lancaster County (Va.) property, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Fehsenfeld, William H., Lancaster County (Va.) property (briefs), 1917 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Fergusson, Lee, case of, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Ferris, I. L., case of, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Fields, William A., case of, 1922-1923 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Fisher, Henry, case of, 1916-1919 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Fisher, Nonie May (administrator for Richard W. Fisher), case of, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Flegenheimer, Melvin, case of, 1922-1923 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Fleming, Charlotte, case of, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Flood, Thomas P. (administrator for Michael J. Flood), case of, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Florsheim, M. B., case of, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Floyd Avenue (Richmond) line track extension, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Food Products Company, case of, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Food Products Company, case of, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Forbes, W. S., financial background of, 1912-1913 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Ford, S. W., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Forrest, S. H., case of, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Foster, George (for Lillian Foster, a minor), case of, 1915 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Foster, Wallace B., case of, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - 14th Street (Richmond) double tracking proposal, 1915 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Frances, M. T., case of, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Freeland, G. H., case of, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Freeman, Lizzie A., case of, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Freeman, Marie L., case of, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Friedman, Celie, case of, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Friedman, D., case of, 1920 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Friel, Catherine, case of, 1922-1923 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Fritzinger, Lucille, case of, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Fritzinger, Mamie, case of, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Fulton Street (Richmond) track extension, 1913 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Cases: General - G, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Cases: General - G, 1924-1925 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Gaines, H. M., case of, 1922-1923 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Gallagher, A. J., case of, 1915 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Garner, Ora E., case of (automobile damages), 1915 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Garner, Ora E., case of (personal injury), 1915 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Garner, Purcell G., case of, 1920 (Box 13, Folder 55a)
    - Garnett, Robert Henry, case of, 1918-1919 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Garrett, E. Pearl, case of, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Garrett, John A., case of, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Garten, J. D., case of, 1920 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Gay, J. Alton, case of, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Gay, Willie Mabel, case of, 1920-1921 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - General Electric Company, case of, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Gerst, Herbert, case of, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Gillis Creek (Richmond) sewer right-of-way dedication, 1914 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Glazier, Hattie C., case of, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Glover, Eva (administrator for Eva Glover), case of, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Coffigan, Gilmer, case of, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Goldwater, L., case of, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Gooch, T. R., Jr., case of, 1915-1916 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Goode, Mary Virginia, case of, 1915 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Goode, Tabby Louise, case of, 1915 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Goodman, A., case of, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Goodman, Thomas F., case of, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Grandy, B. A., case of, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Grant, Walter M., case of, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Graves, Ella Culpepper, case of, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Graves, Stanley H., case of, 1915-1917 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Green, Andrew, case of, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Green, Katherine T., case of, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Green, Lena, case of, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Gregory, H. J., 1921 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Gregory, Herman, case of, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Gregory, W. O., case of, 1920-1921 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Griffin, M. E., case of, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Gumm, H. M. (administrator of Glenn A. Gumm), case of, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Gurley, J. C., case of, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Cases: General - H, 1921-1923 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Cases: General - H, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Cases: General - H, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - H. H. Johnson Company, case of, 1915-1916 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - H. L. Page and Company, case of, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Haggar, Ida M., case of, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Hall, J. B., case of, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Hall, J. W., case of, 1920, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Hall, Maria, case of, 1921, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Hamburger, R., case of, 1918 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Hampton Roads Supply Company, case of, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Hampton Roads Yacht Club, contract cancellation, 1912-1913 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Hancock, E., case of, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Hardee, C. L., case of, 1922-1923 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Harfield, E. E., case of, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Harrell, Gladys, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Harris, William, case of, 1916-1918 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Harrison, Samuel H., case of, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Harrison Transfer Company, case of, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Hartigan, M. A., case of, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Harvey, L. E., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Hawkins, Merritt Lee, case of, 1922-1923 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Hayes, Sadie, case of, 1920, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Haynor, Thomas H., case of, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Haywood, Cecil, case of, 1922, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Heeke, Marie C., case of, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Hemby, H. C., case of, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Henderson, Young and Betham, case of, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Herman, Fritz, case of, 1918 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Hernandez, Eva Virginia, case of, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Hester, E. J. (administrator for Robert Lacy Hester), case of, 1918 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Heth, W. R., Jr., case of, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Hettrick, C., case of, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Hicks, W. D., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Higgins, Eleanor, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Highland Park (Richmond) skip-stop ordinance, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Hill, P. J., case of, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - , 19 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Hirschler, M., case of, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Hoffman, Isaac, case of, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Hogshead, Clifton, case of, 1918-1919 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Holladay, John M., case of, 1920-1921 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Holland, M. D., case of, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Home Steam Laundry, case of (B1821), 1920 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Home Steam Laundry, case of (B1764), 1920 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Hosier, William J. (adminstrator for Elijah Boush), case of, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Howell, Ethel, case of, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Hudgins, M. P., case of, 1920-1921 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Hudgins, R. W., transfer of property deed from Atlantic Coast Terminal Company, 1919-1920 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Hudson, W. H., case of, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Huffines, J. H., case of, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Hull, D. S., settlement of, 1915-1916 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Hull Street (Richmond) cars transfer at Main Street, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Hull Street (Richmond) paving controversy, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Hunt, S. H., case of, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Hurst, Edgar L., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Hutcheson, Victor J., case of, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Hutton, Mary Sandys, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Cases: General - I, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - I. Bluford and Company, case of, 1916-1917 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Ingram, Roxie, case of, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Irwin, W. T. (Irwin's Trading Company), case of, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Isley, D. H., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Cases: General - J, 1921'-1925 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - J. and E. Mahoney, trolley car advertisments in conflict with Prohibition Law, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - J. U. Addenbrook's Sons, Inc., case of (B1652), 1919 (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - J. U. Addenbrook's Sons, Inc., case of (B1473), 1919 (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Jackson, Milton, case of, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Jackson, Thomas, case of, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Jakeman, E. F., case of, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - James, J. S., case of, 1911-1912 (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, 1908-1909 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, August-November 1913 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, January-July 1914 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, August-December 1914 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, 21 December 1914 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, January-February 1915 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, 5 February 1915 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, March-13 October 1915 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, 15 October-November 1915 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, 1916-7 January 1921 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, 10 January-April 1921 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, May 1921-January 1922 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, August 1922-May 1923 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (admissibility briefs), 1915 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (briefs), 1915 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (jury instructions), 1915 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (memorandums), 1913-1915 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (memorandums), 1915 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (memorandums), 1915 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (miscellaneous), 1915 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (Paulus' notes) 1915 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (Paulus' reports), February-March 1915 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (Paulus' statements), February 1915 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (Paulus' statements), 1915 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (plaintiff's note concerning jury misdirection), October 1915 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, n. d. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, n. d. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of, n. d. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (evidenciary photos), n. d. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Jeffress, Thomas F., case of (publications concerning), n. d. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Jellison, O. E., case of, 1920 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Jenkins, Harriett S., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Johns, S. W., case of, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Johnson Accounting Machine Company, 1918 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Johnson, A. L., case of, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Johnson, Alma J., case of, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Johnson, B. J., case of, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Johnson, Catherine, case of, 1916-1918 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Johnson, John R., case of, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 23)